<?xml version = "1.0" ?>
<research>
	
<!-- ======================================== Wand of the Tinkerer /-->
<project id = "WAND_TINKERER" version = "1">
<name>神秘匠之杖</name>
<popupText>[TT] 更多魔力容量</popupText>
<longText>学徒之杖魔力总不够用，于是你决定发挥聪明才智研制一个魔力容量更高的法杖。</longText>
<page type = "text">学习了更多灵气方面的知识后，你制造出魔力容量更高，更适合经验丰富的神秘工匠的法杖。

法杖能容纳500vis的魔力，但其相比学徒之杖，充能速度会变慢许多。</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">WAND_TINKERER</page>
</project>
	 
<!-- ======================================== Gaseous Glowstone /-->
<project id = "GLOWSTONE_GAS" version = "2">
<name>荧光玻璃瓿</name>
<popupText>[TT] 光芒耀大地</popupText>
<longText>纷繁难懂的光学问题的研究进展让你有可能发明一种看不见的光源。</longText>
<page type = "text">纷繁难懂的光学研究进展，让你通过向荧石灌输火要素的力量的方法制造出一种新的看不见的光源。

玻璃瓿里盛放着气态化的魔力荧石，右击后附近会弥漫这种发光的气体，照亮四周。</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">GLOWSTONE_GAS</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Spellbinding Cloth /-->
<project id = "SPELL_CLOTH" version = "1">
<name>祛魔布</name>
<popupText>[TT] 抹掉所有坏运气</popupText>
<longText>你厌倦了在附魔台上赌博。似乎你研究出一种可以抹掉物品上糟糕或者不必要的魔力的魔力布。</longText>
<page type = "text">附魔布匹灌注合适的要素力量后得到的神奇之布。

在合成台中将其和附魔物品一起合成能祛除物品上的魔力，而祛魔布则会消耗一点耐久。</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">SPELL_CLOTH</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Stopwatch of the Timebender /-->
<project id = "STOPWATCH" version = "1">
<name>时间扭曲者的停表</name>
<popupText>[TT] 1.21千兆瓦特!?!</popupText>
<longText>你可能发现了扭曲时间的方法了！</longText>
<page type = "text">你发现一种能将自身所在时间线扭曲的方法，并制作出一种神奇的停表。

右击停表后，你当下的位置，生命以及饱腹度都会记录下来，一分钟后无论你身处何处，只要你身上还带着停表，都将回到之前的位置，以及恢复到之前的生命和饱腹度。 </page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">STOPWATCH</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Wand of Dislocation /-->
<project id = "WAND_DISLOCATION" version = "1">
<name>转移之杖</name>
<popupText>[TT] 看它在这里！看它消失了！</popupText>
<longText>研究了更替之杖的原理后，你发现一种高效移动方块的方法。</longText>
<page type = "text">研究了更替之杖的原理后，你发现一种高效移动方块的方法。

用转移之杖右击方块，会将方块储存进法杖里;再次右击则会将方块放置在你指定的位置。

凡是便携式洞穴都穿透的物品，它都能转移。
注意它的耐久相当低。</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">WAND_DISLOCATION</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Golem Name Tag /-->
<project id = "NAMETAG" version = "1">
<name>傀儡命名牌</name>
<popupText>[TT] 你好!我叫...</popupText>
<longText>一些黑色颜料，加以魔力...好的，你决定你找到办法给你的傀儡起名了。</longText>
<page type = "text">一种有魔力的标牌，可以让你的傀儡仆从显示它们的名字。、

首先你需要在铁砧中为傀儡命名牌改名，改成你需要的名字，之后拿着它左击对应的傀儡即可。</page>
<page type = "arcanecrafting">NAMETAG</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Transmutator /-->
<project id = "TRANSMUTATOR" version = "1">
<name>奥术嬗变台</name>
<popupText>[TT] 不等价交换</popupText>
<longText>灵气研究越发重要起来。你似乎发现一种直接将灵气转换成物质的手段。</longText>
<page type = "text">纷繁复杂的灵气研究的突破让你能够直接抽取魔力，并使用来自附近要素源的要素，直接制造出物质。

这台魔导设备需要放置一个物品作为生成物质的模板。只能是要素构成简单的物品。要制造出新物品，不但需要从灵气中抽取魔力，还需要4倍于该物品的要素。</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">TRANSMUTATOR</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Talisman of Withhold /-->
<project id = "XP_TALISMAN" version = "1">
<name>汇魔之护身符</name>
<popupText>[TT] 专业附魔三十年</popupText>
<longText>僵尸之脑利用得当便能用于储存经验，你试图制作其便携版本。</longText>
<page type = "text">僵尸之脑利用得当便能用于储存经验。你制作的这种护身符虽非完美，但也具有类似功能。

手持护身符按住潜行按键右击可以激活或者关闭护身符：激活的护身符会吸收附近的经验。当携带有空的玻璃瓶的时候，右击护身符，可以释放出经验来填满玻璃瓶得到附魔瓶。</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">XP_TALISMAN</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Infernal Bracelet /-->
<project id = "FIRE_BRACELET" version = "1">
<name>地狱手镯</name>
<popupText>[TT] 掌中炼狱</popupText>
<longText>Knowing the power of an Infernal Furnace, you are trying to figure out how to bring that power with you for better usage.</longText>
<page type = "text">Knowing the ability of an Infernal Furnace to smelt items, you went on to study a way of using that power from your hands.

This bracelet smelts blocks in the world with a right click on them. In order for it to do so, it needs to be charged by right clicking on an active Arcane Bellows, in order to convey the energy of the furnace.</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">FIRE_BRACELET</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Warded Chest /-->
<project id = "WARD_CHEST" version = "1">
<name>守卫者箱子</name>
<popupText>[TT] 尽可能安全</popupText>
<longText>Knowing how safe Warded blocks can be, you are trying to find out a way to make them into item storage.</longText>
<page type = "text">After creating, and working with Warded Blocks, you have discovered a way of making them into storage. This chest is completely safe and can only be opened by the person who placed it. It also has an extended storage space.

Similarly to Warded Blocks, this chest can be removed with a wand. On a negative note, the chest lacks a keyhole.</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">WARD_CHEST</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Smokey Quartz /-->
<project id = "DARK_QUARTZ" version = "1">
<name>烟黑石英</name>
<popupText>[TT] 看起来刚好相反</popupText>
<page type = "text">Smokey Quartz is pretty much Quartz, but negative. All regular blocks that can be made with quartz, can also be made with smokey quartz, and they look black.

Smokey Quartz itself can be made with a piece of coal or charcoal for tinting, and a few pieces of regular nether quartz.</page>
<page type = "crafting">DARK_QUARTZ0</page>
<page type = "crafting">DARK_QUARTZ1</page>
<page type = "crafting">DARK_QUARTZ2</page>
<page type = "crafting">DARK_QUARTZ3</page>
<page type = "crafting">DARK_QUARTZ4</page>
<page type = "crafting">DARK_QUARTZ5</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Sigil of Memories /-->
<project id = "TELEPORTATION_SIGIL" version = "1">
<name>回忆徽章</name>
<popupText>[TT] 每当我想起...</popupText>
<longText>You are planning on creating an item that will allow you return to where you once were before. Some eldritch magic should do...</longText>
<page type = "text">You have created an item that allows you to return to where you've been before. By right clicking with this sigil somewhere, it'll be bound to it.

After a sigil is bound, you can hold right click it, like a bow to charge it and activate it, which teleports you back to where the sigil was bound at. Shattering it in the proceess.</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">TELEPORTATION_SIGIL</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Wand of Uprising /-->
<project id = "WAND_UPRISING" version = "1">
<name>飞升之杖</name>
<popupText>[TT] 我相信，我能飞...</popupText>
<longText>Knowing the power of the Sword of the Zephyr to propel foes away, you are trying to create something that will allow you to propel yourself.</longText>
<page type = "text">Using the knowledge you got from creating the Sword of the Zephyr of propeling things around with air, you created a wand that will propel the holder in the direction that they're looking at.

While someone is flying through the use of this Wand, any acumulated gravitational energy is negated, reseting the fall damage the holder would take.</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">WAND_UPRISING</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Sword of the Condor /-->
<project id = "SWORD_CONDOR" version = "1"> 
<name>秃鹫之剑</name>
<popupText>[TT] 嗖!</popupText>
<longText>Unsatisfacted with the effort you put on the Wand of Uprising, you are trying to combine it with the Sword of the Zephyr in hopes of getting better results.</longText>
<page type = "text">You have found a way of combining the Sword of the Zephyr with your latest creation, the Wand of Uprising. By doing so, you managed to duplicate the effect of the wand used, albeit at a faster speed. It's also possible to sneak right-click to be propeled backwards.

Doing such, however, comes with a few drawbacks. The sword loses it's ability to propel nearby foes, or slow your fall, not to mention that this flight is hard to control. However, by reinforcing the sword with extra Thaumium, it became extremely resistent.</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">SWORD_CONDOR</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Rune Thanatos /-->
<project id = "DEATH_RUNE" version = "1"> 
<name>死神之护身符</name>
<popupText>[TT] The Extra H is for "Hamazing"!</popupText>
<longText>That last time you got blown up by a creeper right next to a lava lake was a big loss. To that, you are trying to research death itself to find ways of securing your belongings.</longText>
<page type = "text">By studying Death itself, you found a way of making use of the powers of item storage you learned from creating Warded Chests, and made a way to secure your belongings upon death.

When you die with this item on you. All that you are carrying gets stored in it. The rune will then stay where you died, it's invulnerable, and doesn't despawn. When you come back to it, your inventory will get reorganized to it's original state before death, as best as possible. The rune will shatter in the process.</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">DEATH_RUNE</page>
</project>


<!-- ======================================== Tool Dynamism /-->
<project id = "ANIMATION_TABLET" version = "1"> 
<name>活化工具</name>
<popupText>[TT] 静若处子，动若脱兔</popupText>
<longText>After learning further into golemancy, you are confident that you can put the Golem Animation Core to create something else than golems...</longText>
<page type = "text">You decided to further discover the uses of Golem Animation Cores, and this is the fruit of that labour.

This tablet can accept an item to animate with mystical energy. Using the left and right buttons in the tablet's interface, you can select to do a left or right click with the item. The button in the bottom controls if the tablet reacts always when it can or just when a redstone signal is applied.

Virtually anything can be animated, including blocks. The type of tool in the tablet also defines how fast something breaks, as expected.</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">ANIMATION_TABLET</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Silk Cutter /-->
<project id = "SILK_SWORD" version = "1"> 
<name>精准之刃</name>
<popupText>[TT] 锋利而光滑</popupText>
<longText>The knowledge you found speaks of a powerful tool that bears the Silk Touch enchantment. You are wondering how to create it, but are sure some cloth will be required.</longText>
<page type = "text">The texts you studied spoke of a powerful tool that beared the Silk Touch enchantment. You seem to have managed to replicate it.

This item acts as an "omnitool" of sorts, it can break virtually anything, but it's not very fast at it. You think enchanting it with Efficiency using an anvil is the logical next step.

Furthermore, after crafting this item, it instantly comes enchanted with the Silk Touch enchantment. The one downside to this is that it can't be enchanted through regular means. It also seems to hold it's magical energy with a extraordinary bond, possibly unbreakable.</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">SILK_SWORD</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Fortunate Maul /-->
<project id = "FORTUNE_MAUL" version = "1"> 
<name>幸运之槌</name>
<popupText>[TT] 非比寻常的猎手</popupText>
<longText>The knowledge you found speaks of a powerful tool that bears the Fortune enchantment. You are wondering how to create it, but are sure some valuable goods will be required.</longText>
<page type = "text">The texts you studied spoke of a powerful tool that beared the Fortune enchantment. You seem to have managed to replicate it.

This item acts as an "omnitool" of sorts, it can break virtually anything, but it's not very fast at it. You think enchanting it with Efficiency using an anvil is the logical next step.

Furthermore, after crafting this item, it instantly comes enchanted with the Fortune III enchantment. The one downside to this is that it can't be enchanted through regular means. It also seems to hold it's magical energy with a extraordinary bond, possibly unbreakable.</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">FORTUNE_MAUL</page>
</project>


<!-- ======================================== Ender Mirror /-->
<project id = "ENDER_MIRROR" version = "1"> 
<name>末影手镜</name>
<popupText>[TT] Another sight</popupText>
<longText>After learning how to transport items using Hand Mirrors, you are thinking you can apply that knowledge to the Ender Chests.</longText>
<page type = "text">You have put the knowledge acquired from constructing the Magic Hand Mirror into good use, and applied it to the Ender Chests.

This mirror, for a small cost of vis from the local aura allows you to access your ender chest inventory without needing to place it down yourself.</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">ENDER_MIRROR</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Goliath's Leggings /-->
<project id = "GOLIATH_LEGS" version = "1"> 
<name>巨人护腿</name>
<popupText>[TT] 巨人的护腿</popupText>
<longText>You are thinking you can create more protective robes using the Thaumaturge's Robes you already know how to make.</longText>
<page type = "text">Making use of the Thaumaturge's Robes you created, you futher worked on them, creating new leggings. These leggings protect the wearer from all incoming damage, by reducing it by 1.

Futhermore, when the wearer would die by a crushing blow when they have more than 2.5 hearts, they stay barely alive with half a heart. 

They also give a more powerful vis reduction.</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">GOLIATH_LEGS</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Gaseous Tenebrae /-->
<project id = "DARK_GAS" version = "1">
<name>暗影玻璃瓿</name>
<popupText>[TT] 黑暗在弥漫</popupText>
<longText>After having learned how to create Gaseous Glowstone, you are thinking about making air that's dark. You are confident that it's possible, and that the other alchemical material is required.</longText>
<page type = "text">You have studied the intricacies of the Shadow, and found out a way to create gaseous darkess by infusing Smokey Quartz with the raw power. 

This phial contains a concentrated extract of Gaseous Tenebrae, that can be released through a right click, and will spread relatively fast in the nearby area, darkening it.</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">DARK_GAS</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Fume Dissipator /-->
<project id = "GAS_REMOVER" version = "1">
<name>暗影驱散器</name>
<popupText>[TT] 凡尘大地本如是</popupText>
<longText>After knowing Gaseous glowstone and Tenebrae, you are thinking it might be possible to get rid of them in an easy manner. Researching the components of the two gases would be the logical next step, you think.</longText>
<page type = "text">After knowing both the Gaseous Glowstone and Tenebrae, you are thinking it's becoming a hassle to get rid of it. With this item, by shift-right clicking on it, all the nearby gas will get dissipated.</page>
<page type = "arcanecrafting">GAS_REMOVER</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Talisman of Remedium /-->
<project id = "CLEANSING_TALISMAN" version = "1">
<name>驱散之护身符</name>
<popupText>[TT] 比牛奶好!</popupText>
<longText>By studying the elements of life and body, you are confident you can make an item to purify yourself.</longText>
<page type = "text">You have studied life and the body and found that through the application of magic you can protect yourself from harmful outside influences by redirecting these effects to another place. This talisman will dispell most harmful effects on the holder, at the cost of vis from the local aura.

To enable or disable this ability, one would shift-right click on it. As expected, it only works whilst enabled.</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">CLEANSING_TALISMAN</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Fluxometer /-->
<project id = "FLUX_DETECTOR" version = "1">
<name>咒波罗盘</name>
<popupText>[TT] 可见咒波</popupText>
<longText>After research of the flux itself, you think that you can make use of one of your early discoveries, the Thaumometer, to measure the flux.</longText>
<page type = "text">Through the research of the flux itself, and through usage of one of your early discoveries, the Thaumomenter, you managed to discover an upgrade for it.

This new detector, the Fluxometer can measure the flux in the nearest relevant node. Whilst looking at the Fluxometer with Goggles of Revealing, the holder can see what flux is in the air. The flux displays as icons, the opacity of each icon indicates how much of that aspect is in the aura. If you look close, you can see maxed out aspects as a bit unstable.</page>
<page type = "arcanecrafting">FLUX_DETECTOR</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Lost Enchantments /-->
<project id = "LOST_ENCHANTS" version = "1">
<name>失落附魔技术</name>
<popupText>[TT] 新型魔法</popupText>
<longText>The pieces of knowledge you have been connecting speak of extremely powerful enchantments on the various schools of magic. You don't know what might come out of this, but you are sure that you would need to study various different items.</longText>
<page type = "text">Extensive research of lost knowledge revealed a set of four very powerful enchantments.

These enchantments can not be enchanted trough the regular means of using an enchanting table, rather, they would need to be created by the usage of an infusion altar. Furthermore, only one of these enchantments can be applied to a specific item at any given time.</page>
<page type = "text">Freezing: Any entity hit with this sword will recieve a freezing effect, imparing their movement. Being set on fire will negate this.

Soulbringer: When a sword imbuded with this hits an undead, there's a chance for that undead to get possessed and succumb to your side.

Vampirism: Upon hitting an entity, a quarter of the damage dealt will be absorbed by the attacker.

Ashes: The only of the four enchantments that isn't only for weapons. Any item that has this enchantment, upon being broken, it'll be revived back to life, at the cost of this enchantment and two random others.</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">ENCHANT_FREEZING</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">ENCHANT_SOULBRINGER</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">ENCHANT_VAMPIRISM</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">ENCHANT_ASHES</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Phantom Stone Blocks /-->
<project id = "PHANTOM_STONE" version = "1">
<name>幻影石块</name>
<popupText>[TT]这是真的?</popupText>
<longText>You are not quite sure what you are doing, you think you might have found something, that's about it...</longText>
<page type = "text">You don't know how you managed to do it, but you have found a way of creating blocks that exist in non-euclidean space.

These blocks are based on the design you had put together for Warded Stone Blocks, they can only be broken by the player who placed them, using a wand. 

However, there's a particularity to these. They have no physical boundaries for the player who placed them, allowing them to walk trough these blocks as if they didn't exist. For everything else, they act as normal blocks.</page>
<page type = "arcanecrafting">PHANTOM_STONE</page>
</project>
</research>
